 var data = [{
   "hanja": "果刀",
   "jei_set": "가01",
   "mean": "과도",
   "sense": "과일을 깎는 칼",
   "question": "( )刀",
   "answer": "果"
 }, {
   "hanja": "大門",
   "jei_set": "가02",
   "mean": "대문",
   "sense": "큰 문",
   "question": "( )門",
   "answer": "大"
 }, {
   "hanja": "馬車",
   "jei_set": "가03",
   "mean": "마차",
   "sense": "말이 끄는 수레",
   "question": "( )車",
   "answer": "馬"
 }, {
   "hanja": "明月",
   "jei_set": "가04",
   "mean": "명월",
   "sense": "밝은 달",
   "question": "明( )",
   "answer": "月"
 }, {
   "hanja": "木石",
   "jei_set": "가05",
   "mean": "목석",
   "sense": "나무와 돌",
   "question": "( )石",
   "answer": "木"
 }, {
   "hanja": "山林",
   "jei_set": "가06",
   "mean": "산림",
   "sense": "산과 숲. 산에 있는 숲",
   "question": "( )林",
   "answer": "山"
 }, {
   "hanja": "男女",
   "jei_set": "가07",
   "mean": "남녀",
   "sense": "남자와 여자",
   "question": "男( )",
   "answer": "女"
 }, {
   "hanja": "水中",
   "jei_set": "가08",
   "mean": "수중",
   "sense": "물 속",
   "question": "( )中",
   "answer": "水"
 }, {
   "hanja": "人力車",
   "jei_set": "가09",
   "mean": "인력거",
   "sense": "사람의 힘으로 끄는 수레",
   "question": "( )力車",
   "answer": "人"
 }, {
   "hanja": "牛耳",
   "jei_set": "가10",
   "mean": "우이",
   "sense": "소의 귀",
   "question": "牛( )",
   "answer": "耳"
 }, {
   "hanja": "耳目",
   "jei_set": "가11",
   "mean": "이목",
   "sense": "귀와 눈",
   "question": "耳( )",
   "answer": "目"
 }, {
   "hanja": "下人",
   "jei_set": "가12",
   "mean": "하인",
   "sense": "남의 밑에서 부림을 받는 사람",
   "question": "( )人",
   "answer": "下"
 }, {
   "hanja": "一日",
   "jei_set": "가13",
   "mean": "일일",
   "sense": "하루. 그 달의 첫째 날",
   "question": "一( )",
   "answer": "日"
 }, {
   "hanja": "一男一女",
   "jei_set": "가14",
   "mean": "일남일녀",
   "sense": "아들 하나 딸 하나",
   "question": "( )男( )女",
   "answer": "一"
 }, {
   "hanja": "子女",
   "jei_set": "가15",
   "mean": "자녀",
   "sense": "아들과 딸",
   "question": "( )女",
   "answer": "子"
 }, {
   "hanja": "田畓",
   "jei_set": "가16",
   "mean": "전답",
   "sense": "밭과 논",
   "question": "( )畓",
   "answer": "田"
 }, {
   "hanja": "天下",
   "jei_set": "가17",
   "mean": "천하",
   "sense": "하늘 아래",
   "question": "( )下",
   "answer": "天"
 }, {
   "hanja": "下車",
   "jei_set": "가18",
   "mean": "하차",
   "sense": "차에서 내림",
   "question": "下( )",
   "answer": "車"
 }, {
   "hanja": "火力",
   "jei_set": "가19",
   "mean": "화력",
   "sense": "불의 힘",
   "question": "( )力",
   "answer": "火"
 }, {
   "hanja": "休日",
   "jei_set": "가20",
   "mean": "휴일",
   "sense": "쉬는 날",
   "question": "( )日",
   "answer": "休"
 }
];
